Alright I'll be teaching you about the Nanbokushou period.
The Kemmu restoration of 1333 was the starting point of the period.
Seki-kun, the guy who sits next to me, is always with playing with something.
1st Period
Domino
Domino.
The Kemmu Restoration is defined as
Emperor Daigo came into power and became the center of politics.
The honoring of the aristocrats
led to the disregard of the historical custom of samurai culture.
the restoration was rejected by the
warrior class and animosity spread.
The samurai, Ashikaga Takauji,
fought to return power to the warrior class...
Seki-kun.
Hey! You really shouldn't be doing that.
The teacher's going to see you.
You do know that our history teacher,
Adachi-sensei, gets really scary
when he's mad, right?
You really shouldn't be
doing that right now.
Huh?
What is with that, "I'm concentrating, be quiet!" reaction?
That's strange!
Seki-kun, you're in no position
to be warning anyone right now.
Dominos.
You're seriously playing
with dominos during class!
What's that? A see-saw?
Talk about going all out...
Next to read is Yokoi.
Yokoi, can't you hear me?!
Y-Yes!
Such antagonizing eyes
He's staring at me intensely with those antagonizing eyes!
This is definitely awkward!
You shouldn't be playing with dominoes during class!
Needed? Is an apology really needed?
Is something wrong, Yokoi?
No, nothing's wrong.
History
Amazing!
I think it'd be easier by far if he studied normally.
Artillery Shell
Five-Colored Dragon
Danger
Whoa!
Seki-kun! You can't use that set-up.  You'll get in big trouble.
This is a classroom!
Please reconsider this!
Stop! Stop!
An S-curve!
A multi-level crossing!
This isn't the time for a triumphant fist!
Stairs?
A c-cable car?!
No! At this rate, it's gonna head straight for
the grand finale: the firework!
It's going to fire off!
Oh. So that part just
plays out in his head.
Hey, Yokoi!
Do you even intend to take this class?
I-It wasn't me! Um, Seki-kun
was... Seki-kun was...
Seki-kun, Master
of Killing Time
Seki-kun, Master of Killing Time!