doki doki hara hara hounano
The way that the heart beats
hajimete doku made watashi kimochi matte asobu no
my feelings are starting to play badly
mushi mushi muri muri totsuzen
suddenly not so hot hot and humid
hajimaru daisu ateiwasetai
tomeni subete
the whole thing stop
wo kaketeru no
running
Mainichi
Daily
da ime ii wa
A good nickname would be
okiraku maite e
would be carefree wind.
esu otoko no
Understand guys'
towoke dan
wo shitero dan
dame dai yo zettai
absolutely wrong
dai ie mi ha
A good nickname would be
takke totsu
umechau kimi no
your birth
honto kimi natte
to become the real you
oto wa
guys are
nani suru no
what are you doing?
Kuki yomozen doushite made jibun
sekai mujyaki hayari gomerun no
the world's innocent fashion
honto ni baka baka so nano energy
really that energy used to be foolish
nani kamo tono kano tsukare ba ii
whatever you do to become tired is fine.
ii no ni otoko no ko
such a good boy
ote wakarana ii
I don't understand
mainichi
daily
da ime ii wa
A good nickname would be
okiraku mai ni aku
between the grip of the wind.
kore ii cho wo
this fine work
watashi datte
all because of me.
Tsuki yatte ranai
zettai...
absolutely
da ime ii wa
A good nickname would be
maki koman na ii tetemo
hotokenai
oshiete
Teach me
sono zugin onaru no
watashi wa
I
itsudemo
always
watashi de
doing myself
itai no ni
an injury